[Music]
in this final quarter we really really
need to turn in a good call so otherwise
when our growth is not going to be very
very good this year if we're concerning
good growth and our bancassurance
channel is having an absolutely
fantastic year so if we can just
complement that in agency in the last
quarter the chances are we'll definitely
get to number seven and we could even
get to number six do we want that
[Music]
I'm going to cut the keys and enjoy it I
want bubble tea
welcome to time area
[Music]
happy city also name the city that never
sleeps
yeah I remember
[Music]
across
[Applause]
[Music]
I can subscribe and comment down below
you